Princeton Football Films Collection, 1935-2012(bulk 1935-1990): Finding Aid AC297
University Archives
- Princeton Football Film Reels, 1935-1990; 2187 items
  - 1976-1977, 198 items
    - 1976 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1976 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1976 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1976 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1976 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1976 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1976 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1976 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1976 None (Miscellaneous), 1 item (Item 1976 None (Miscellaneous))
    - 1976 None (Miscellaneous), 1 item (Item 1976 None (Miscellaneous))
    - 1976 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1976 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1976 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1976 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1976 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1976 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1976 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1976 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1977 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1977 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1977 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1977 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1977 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1977 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1977 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1977 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Columbia (Offense 3), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Offense 3))
    - 1977 Columbia (Offense 4), 1 item (Item 1977 Columbia (Offense 4))
    - 1977 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1977 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1977 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1977 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1977 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1977 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1977 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1977 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1977 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1977 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1977 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1977 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1977 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1977 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1977 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1977 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1977 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1977 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1977 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1977 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1977 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1977 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1977 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1977 Yale (Offense 2))
  - 1978-1979, 201 items
    - 1978 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1978 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1978 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1978 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1978 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1978 Colgate (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Full Game 4))
    - 1978 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1978 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1978 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1978 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1978 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1978 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1978 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1978 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1978 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1978 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1978 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1978 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1978 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1978 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1978 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1978 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1978 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1978 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Defense), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Defense))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Kicking))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1978 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1978 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1978 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1978 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1978 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1978 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1978 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1978 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1979 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1979 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1979 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1979 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1979 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1979 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1979 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1979 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1979 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1979 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1979 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1979 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1979 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1979 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1979 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1979 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1979 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1979 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1979 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1979 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1979 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1979 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1979 None (Practice/Scrimage 1), 1 item (Item 1979 None (Practice/Scrimage 1))
    - 1979 None (Practice/Scrimage 2), 1 item (Item 1979 None (Practice/Scrimage 2))
    - 1979 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1979 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1979 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1979 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1979 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1979 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Kicking))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Kicking))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1979 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1979 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1979 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1979 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1979 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1979 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1979 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1979 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1979 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Offense 2))